

52, 11th Main Road Banashankari Stage II Bengaluru, INDIA 560070 ▼ WHC9+8C BSK

Image ■ varungupta3009@gmail.com

+91 97398 56528

@ varungupta3009

(## //VRG.design/

Experience



Penetration Tester

Center for Information Security, Forensics and Cyber Resilience May 2020 - Present (4 mos)



Student Lead in Network Security and Web Development

Developer Student Clubs • PES University Jan 2019 - Present (1 yr 8 mos)



Software Engineer

Mindtree

Jul 2019 - Feb 2020 (8 mos)

Education



Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering 2017 - 2021



R. V. PU College

Pre-University, Affiliated to NCERT, New Delhi, Computer Science



Carmel School, Padmanabhanagar

ICSE, New Delhi — SSLC, Karnataka 2002 – 2015

Publications & Awards

Software Implementation of an Automatic Movable Road Barrier

IEEE, October 2019, ISBN: 978-1-7281-1576-4

Prof. C N R Rao Merit Scholarship

PES University, November 2019

Licenses and Certifications

Associate Cloud Engineer

Google, August 2020

Languages

English Hindi Kannada

Hobbies

Reading

(A) Gaming

W Virtual Aviation

|--|

Knowledge and Skills

Python 3 Experience Skill	
JavaScript Experience Skill	
C/C++ Experience Skill	
Java, C#, Go Experience Skill	
Frontend Design a Experience Skill	nd Development
Full-Stack Web De Experience Skill	velopment
Angular (TS), Reac Experience Skill	t (JS/TS)
WordPress, CMS Experience	
Adobe Photoshop Experience Skill	& Illustrator
Adobe After Effect Experience Skill	ts and Premiere Pro
Blender, Pixar Ren Experience	derman
Cloud Architechtu	re (GCP)

About me

I am a programmer and experienced web-developer, fluent in Python, C++, C#, Go with over 9 years of experience in Python and C++, and moderately versed in 7 other languages. I am a polymath and love to explore and try new technologies and fiddling with anything related to computer. I am also a graphics designer and a hobbyist hacker.

I recommend checking out my LinkedIn Profile for real-time accurate information and to stay updated on any changes.

Experience

Skill

